internet-success-system.com 2006-12-30

# 

    PRIVACY POLICY
    
    Last Updated: May 1, 2003
    
    Hunteridge, Inc.
    
    For websites: 
    
    Hunteridge.com
    Market-Soft.com
    JVdealmaker.com
    TopMarketingExpertsTellAll.com
    SpecialsAndDeals.com
    SwiftKickInTheButt.com
    FreeResaleRightsVault.com
    Internet-Success-System.com

    Hunteridge, Inc. strives to offer its website visitors the many
    advantages of Internet technology and to
    provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may
    use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail
    address, street address, telephone number) subject to the
    terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter,
    or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party.
    Period."
    
    How we gather information from users
    
    How we collect and store information depends on the page
    you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to
    participate and the services provided. For example, you may
    be asked to provide information when you register for
    access to certain portions of our site or request certain
    features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase.
    You may provide information when you participate in
    sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms,
    and other interactive areas of our site. Like most Web
    sites, Hunteridge, Inc. also collects
    information automatically and through the use of electronic
    tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example,
    we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or
    use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information
    from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store
    your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-
    enter that information each time you visit, or may control
    the number of times you encounter a particular
    advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt
    additional technology, we may also gather information
    through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not
    to provide us with information, for example by setting your
    browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may
    be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be
    asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may
    not be able to customize the site's features according to
    your preferences.
    
    What we do with the information we collect
    
    Like other Web publishers, we collect information to
    enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content
    and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share
    your information with anyone.
    
    Aggregated Information (information that does not
    personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For
    example, we may combine information about your usage
    patterns with similar information obtained from other users
    to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which
    pages are visited most or what features are most
    attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be
    shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again,
    this information does not include any Personally
    Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to
    identify you individually.
    
    We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected
    Hunteridge, Inc.) to communicate with
    you about your registration and customization preferences;
    our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and
    products offered by Hunteridge, Inc. and
    other topics we think you might find of interest. 
    
    Personally Identifiable Information collected by Hunteridge, Inc.
    may also be used for
    other purposes, including but not limited to site
    administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce
    transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests,
    and other communications with you. Certain third parties
    who provide technical support for the operation of our site
    (our Web hosting service for example) may access such
    information. We will use your information only as permitted
    by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to
    develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner
    with other companies or businesses. In such transactions,
    user information may be among the transferred assets. We
    may also disclose your information in response to a court
    order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably
    required to do so by law, in connection with the collection
    of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement
    authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary.
    Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to
    disclosure in such cases.
    
    Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements
    
    Hunteridge, Inc. expects its partners,
    advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our
    users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our
    partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content
    providers accessible through our site, may have their own
    privacy and data collection policies and practices. For
    example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or
    view as part of a frame on a Hunteridge, Inc. page, certain content
    that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through
    Hunteridge, Inc. you may be introduced to, or be able to
    access, information, Web sites, features, contests or
    sweepstakes offered by other parties. Hunteridge, Inc. is not responsible
    for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the
    applicable privacy policies of those third parties when
    providing information on a feature or page operated by a
    third party.
    
    While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners
    or other third parties may use cookies or other technology
    to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve
    information about you. For example, some of our advertising
    is served by third parties and may include cookies that
    enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a
    particular advertisement before. Other features available
    on our site may offer services operated by third parties
    and may use cookies or other technology to gather
    information. Hunteridge, Inc. does not
    control the use of this technology by third parties or the
    resulting information, and is not responsible for any
    actions or policies of such third parties.
    
    You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose
    Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in
    chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can
    be collected and used by third parties without our
    knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other
    individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond
    the control of Hunteridge, Inc. and this
    policy.
    
    Children
    
    Hunteridge, Inc. does not knowingly
    collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from
    or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If
    we discover we have received any information from a child
    under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that
    information immediately. If you believe Hunteridge, Inc.
    has any information from or about anyone
    under 13, please contact us at the address listed below.
    
    Contacting Us.
    
    We can be reached by contacting:
    
    Email: privacy@Hunteridge.com
    
    Changes to this Policy
    
    Hunteridge, Inc. reserves the right to
    change this policy at any time. Please check this page
    periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site
    following the posting of changes to these terms will mean
    you accept those changes. Information collected prior to
    the time any change is posted will be used according to the
    rules and laws that applied at the time the information was
    collected.
    
    Governing law
    
    This policy and the use of this Site are governed by
    Florida law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree
    to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually
    agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Dade City,
    Florida. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees
    associated with the mediation will be shared equally by
    each of us.
    
    If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually
    satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit
    the dispute to binding arbitration at the following
    location: Dade City, Florida, under the rules of the
    American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award
    rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court
    with jurisdiction to do so.
    
    Hunteridge, Inc. is controlled, operated
    and administered entirely within Hunteridge, Inc. 
    
    This statement and the policies
    outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any
    contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any
    party.
